Finding aid to the Alexander C. Sanger papers SSC.MS.00654
Sophia Smith Collection
- Writings and Interviews, 1970-2016; 4
  - Letters to the Editor, 1996-2011; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Article, "Mandate for Reform", 1970; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Article, "No More Taj Mahals", 2010 April 21; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Beyond Choice book proposal, 2001; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Beyond Choice materials, 2001; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "Reaching Out" articles, 2006-2009; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Beyond Choice notes and correspondence, 2001; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Beyond Choice reader comments, 2001; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Review of article, "Why the Millennium Development Goals Included Maternal Mortality Reduction", 2010; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Greenland/climate change article, 2000; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Children's drawings, undated; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - South Dakota article, 2006; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "Two Funerals", 2006; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - "Sam Alito's Fictional Memoir", undated; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Article, "Vision for PP", 1995 December; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Article, "In Search of Cal Ripkin in Beijing", 1995; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Article, about ACS, 2000, 2001; 2 folders (2 folder) (Box 20, Folder 3, 5)
  - Articles and op eds by ACS, 2000-2009; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 4, 6, 8-11, 13, 17-19)
  - Interview, "The Pill", 2001; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Article, Thomas Thacher, 2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Article, Lawrence Lader, 2006; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Articles, Charles Brush III, 2006; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Article, "Lesser of Two Evils", 2006; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Audio recording, Interview, Radio New Zealand, 2010 May; 1 items (1 CD) (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - March on Washington, 2004 April 23-25; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Professional Activities, 1974-2017; 5
  This series contains material on Alexander Sanger's involvement with law in general, Planned Parenthood NYC, the People Count project, International Planned Parenthood Federation, the Toulmin Foundation, and the Wellesley Center for Women.
  - Law career, A
    - White and Case office directories, 1974-1988; 3 folders (3 folders) (Box 31, Folder 1, 2, 3)
    - "Net Worth" articles, 1981-1983; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - "Estate planning and will drafting", 1981-1982; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 31, Folder 5, 6)
    - "Outline of charitable lead trusts", 1982; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Tax conference, 1982; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - "Conformity of NY Estate and Gift tax to federal rules", 1983; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - White and Case documents, "Objectives of Good Estate Planning", 1984-1987; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - "Estate planning, will drafting, and gift taxes", 1983; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - White and Case, "Should you leave it all to the children?", 1987; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - PPNYC, B
    - Curriculum modules: Women's Health..., 1987; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Margaret Sanger Center proposal, 1989; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - BrainReserve report, 1990; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Human resources, 1991; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - PPNYC President and CEO info, 1991; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - ACS Notes, 1991; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Board lunches, 1991; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Office diary, 1991; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Board lunches - ACS personal notes, 1992; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - ACS Notes, 1992; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - ACS notes and itinerary for Planned Parenthood to Phillippines, 1992 February; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - ACS notes, 1993; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Profiles - Executive Director misc material, 1990-1995; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Board profiles - retreat goals, 1994; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Board profile - governance, 1990-1993; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Profiles - BOARD misc materials, 1992-1993; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - PPNYC Media Scrapbooks, 1993-1994 (Box 94)
    - Board - strategic planning, 1994; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Board diversity task force materials and report, 1994; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Job description for President/CEO, 1995; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Evaluation/history ACS, 1995 June; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - 5 year history and vision for future, 1995; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Board orientation materials, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Executive board pamphlets, 1997, 1999; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - PPNYC Security
      - Clinic access laws, 1992-1999; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - PPNYC security, 1996; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Case for clinic renovations, 1996 June 11; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Clinic access laws, 2000; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Clinic security, 1999; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Acquiring 26 Bleeker Street, 1996; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - PPNYC Security misc, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Organizational literature, 1990-2005; 5 folders (5 folders) (Box 35, Folder 1-5)
    - PPNYC Administrative and Financial, 1990-1997 (Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50)
      - North Manhattan Health Services Planning Project, 1990 May (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Hay Management Consultants Study: "Impact of Stress Resulting From Anti-Choice...", 1990 December (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - A Report on the First Year of An Experience on Preventative Education, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Financial Statements, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Analysis of Executive Director Turnover, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Summary Reports, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Business Plans and Reports, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Business Plans and Reports, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Annual Plans, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Development Business Plan and Reports, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - PPNYC Administrative Report, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - PPNYC Annual Report, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Affirmative Action Plan, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - PPNYC Financial Statements, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - EEOC Report, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - CL-7 Report, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Finance and Administrative Business Plans & Reports, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Public Affairs Business Plans & Reports, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - PPNYC Strategic Planning, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - PPNYC Annual Plans, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Reports to the Board, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Program Descriptions and Evaluations, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Employee Evaluations, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Employee Resignations, Severance, and Replacement Information, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - International Business Plans and Reports, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous Reports, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - PPNYC Public Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Public Affairs: Business Plans, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - PPNYC Reports, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Business Plans, Sanger Executive Office, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Business Plans / Program Services, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Public Affairs Department, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - PPNYC Financial Statements, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Re-certification Materials, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Re-certification Materials, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Annual Business Plan, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Reports to the Board, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - CL-7 Report, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - PPNYC Board Retreat Preparations, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - PPNYC Board Retreat, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - PPNYC Business Plans and Personal Reports, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Program Services Business Plans and Reports, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - PPNYC Fundraising & Development Business Plan, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - International Business Plans and Reports, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - PPNYC Performance Appraisals and Strategic Business Planning, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - PPNYC Annual Report, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Business Plans, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - "Family Planning: Creating A Public Policy Agenda for NYC", 1993 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Security Issues, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Organizational Development and Business Plan Reports, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - International Business and Reports, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - PPNYC Development Business Plan and Reports, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Finance & Administration, Business Plans and Reports, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Financial Statements, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Annual Report, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Program Services Annual Report, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Business Plan, Program Services, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Market Research, We Care, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Market Research, We Care, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Program Services / Business Plan and Reports, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Program Services / Task Force Notes, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Public Affairs / Business Plans and Reports, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Budget, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Reports to the Board, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - CL-7 Report, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - EEOC Reports, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Financial Statements, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - CL-7 Reports, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - EEOC Reports, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Reports to the Board, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Security Procedures, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Annual Report, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - ACS notes, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Executive Plans, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Public Affairs, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Program Services and Business Plans, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Program Services Report, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Program Services Plans and Reports, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Program Services Plans and Reports, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Finance Business Plans and Report, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - International Business Plan and Reports, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Organization Development Business Plans and Reports, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Financial Statements, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Budget, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Budget, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Affiliate Speaking Engagements, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - PPNYC Annual Report, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - PPNYC Public Affairs, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Reports to the Board, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - 5 Year Agency Summary, 1991-1995 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - 5 Year Agency Summary, 1991-1995 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Program Services, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Program Services, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Program Services, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Finance and Administration, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Development, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Development, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - International, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Japan trip, 1997 April (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Tanzania / Zanzibar trip, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - PPNYC Board Reports, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - PPNYC Human Resources, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - PPNYC 1995 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Public Affairs, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Budget, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - PPFA President Search, 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - PPNYC Development, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Finance and Administration, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - PPNYC Annual Report, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Public Policy Summit, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Public Policy Summit, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - PPNYC President's Calendar, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Public Affairs, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - May Del Rio, VP of Public Affairs notes, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Reports and Proceedings on Preventing Pregnancy, AIDS, Violence, 1996 October 30-31 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Program Services, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Program Services, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Alexander C. Sanger notes, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Human Resources, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - International, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Board Reports, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Strategic Planning, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - PPNYC Development, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Public Policy Summit, National Survey, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Board Manual, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Board Manual, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Board Manual, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Board Manual, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Calendar, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Human Resources, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Education, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Development, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Priorities, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Executive staff - first retreat, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Executive staff - second retreat, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Executive staff - third retreat, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - PPNYC Reproductive Health - Managed Care Policy Series, Vol 1-3, 1997 April; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - PPNYC Capital Campaign, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Clinical services, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Public affairs, 1997; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 52, Folder 3, 4)
      - Board reports, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - International, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - PPNYC annual report, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - PPNYC yearly, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - PPFA summit, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - PPFA, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - PP International - China, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - PPNYC evaluations, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - PP Summit, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - PPNYC Annual Report, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Mission statement, 1998; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 54, Folder 6, 7)
    - PP global partner research, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - PPNYC Board (BD)/Council (CL) manual, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Clinical services, 1998; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 55, Folder 1, 2)
    - International, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Responsible Choice Action Agenda, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - "Talking with young adults about sexuality", 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Board reports, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - ACS diary, 1997 September - 1998 July; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Phone log, 1997-1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Misc executive staff documents, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Public affairs, 1998; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 56, Folder 4, 5)
    - Partnership in leadership, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Development, 1998; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 57, Folder 2, 3)
    - Executive staff meetings, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Administrative calendar, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Security memo, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Education, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Human resources, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Alexander Sanger evaluation, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - PPNYC: Mapping the Future, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - PPNYC Board/Council manual, 1998; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 58, Folder 1, 2)
    - Capital Campaign report, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - PPNYC financial, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - PPNYC budget, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Leadership workshop, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Nominating committee materials, 1998-1999; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - President's Day / Phone Log, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Calendar, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - PPNYC - Executive Staff, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - PPNYC Public Affairs, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Alexander Sanger Evaluation, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Peter Wildrotter, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - PP International Family Planning: An Executive Summary, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - 2025: Future Research for the PP Movement, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Development, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Healthpass, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - PPNYC staff list, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Clinical Services, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Clinical Services, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Clinical Services, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Clinical Services, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - PPNYC advertisements, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Operating Plans, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Operating Plans, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Scenarios, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Board reports, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Financial Statement, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Budget Planning, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Budget Planning, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Finance and Administration, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - International, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Executive staff retreat, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Finance: Boro Hall Assessment, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Memos to Board, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - PPNYC Annual Report, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - International, 1997-1999 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Board Meetings PPNYC, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Alexander Sanger PPNYC Resignation, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Miscelleanous, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Alexander Sanger's 10 year history and resume, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - ACS Personal, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - NY State Affiliates of PP, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Public Impact Team, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Othmer Institute, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Schneiderman Lectures, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Contributions to outside organizations, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Pension, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Pension, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - L12 ORR, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Family Planning Advocates, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - PPNYC Annual Report, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Human Resources, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Press Materials, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - "Interim Forever" PPNYC Anthem, undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Event Invitations, 1995-2001 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Misc Media Events, 1991-1998 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Dedication of Bleeker Street, 1992 June 10 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Misc Media Placements / Events, 1991-2004 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Alexander Sanger Speech Talking Points, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Alexander Sanger Speech Talking Points, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Alexander Sanger Speech Talking Points, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Alexander Sanger Speech Talking Points, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Alexander Sanger Speech Talking Points, 2000-2001 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Alexander Sanger Speech Talking Points, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - PPNYC Press Statements, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Press Releases, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Media Placements, 1990 December - 1991 May (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Media Placements, 1991 June - December (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Media Placements Report and Selected Articles, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Media Placements, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Media Placements Report and Selected Articles, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Media Placements Report and Selected Articles, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Media Placements Report and Selected Articles, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Media Placements PPNYC, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Media Placements PPNYC, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Media Placements, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Media Placements PPNYC, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Media Placements, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Media Placements, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Media Placements, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Media Placements, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Media Placements, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Media Placements, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Media Placements, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Media Placements, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Media Placements, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Media Placements, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Media Placements, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Media Placements, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Media Placements, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Media Placements, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Media Placements, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Media Placements, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Media Placements, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Media Placements, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Media Placements, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - ACS Newsclips, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - ACS Newsclips, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - ACS Newsclips, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Media Placements, 2004-2005 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Media Placements, 2011 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - PPNYC Impact Study - Abortion Stats, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Patient Survey, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Potential Consumers Poll, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Political Poll, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Women(12-19) Poll, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Women(18-45) Poll, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Women(18-45) Poll, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - NYS Penn and Schoen Polls, Fact Finders, 1981-1990, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Moran Poll, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - NYS Poll, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - PPNYC Abortion Polls, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - PPFA Harris Poll - Image and Marketing Polls, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Family Planning Media Consortium Qualitative Research Major Findings, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - American Teens Speak Poll, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 2)